=Lady Liberty=
=Episode 8=
Coming.
Mom.
He Han is inside talking to your dad.
When I got here,
your dad wouldn't open the door.
Good thing He Han showed up.
He's so thoughtful.
He never forgets
our birthdays.
Of course. What took you so long?
I've been talking to your dad.
I told you not to come.
Why are you here?
When did you say that?
Yesterday.
Did you?
Go home right now.
Your mom asked me to stay for lunch.
Are you done talking?
If so, leave now.
If not, you have five minutes.
I'm here for your own good.
To lighten the mood.
Isn't it nice to get along?
That's only temporary.
The drama is coming.
You're just in the way.
How am I in the way?
- Getting along...
- Mom.
Something came up for He Han.
- He has to leave.
- I'm fine, Mrs. Lin.
Aren't you staying for lunch?
- Yeah, just a few bites.
- Talk to him later.
Don't give him an attitude.
I have to take your mom home.
- I can take you home.
- The food is ready.
- Food is ready.
- Food is ready. Come on.
Okay, Mrs. Lin.
Just a few bites.
Lunch's ready, Mr. Lin.
You'll hold things up.
They'll be waiting for you.
Let them wait.
Drink less alcohol.
Have some juice.
Okay.
Family together,
healthy and happy.
Isn't it great?
Come on.
I said keep it simple,
but you made a feast again.
You're tired cooking it,
and we're tired eating it.
Can't you ever just relax?
It's a birthday.
You're like this birthday or not.
Dad.
Okay.
You and Mom
don't eat together every day, right?
If you see something you like,
eat more.
If not, don't eat it.
Put up with it.
I worked hard to make extra dishes
so we could finally
have a nice family dinner
and be happy.
Why should he have to "put up with it"?
Come on, eat.
I'll say it again.
Just because you work hard,
doesn't mean we'll be happy.
You should go.
If we really start fighting,
lunch will be ruined.
This isn't fighting.
We're just expressing opinions. Right?
This is great. I love this.
Family together,
talking things out.
It's lively and fun.
Mr. Lin, come on.
Cheers.
Happy birthday. To your health.
And thanks for fixing my erhu.
What erhu?
A new hobby.
He Han appreciates our folk music.
That erhu is a good one.
The resonator was cracked.
Fixing it was no big deal.
Thank you.
Good thing He Han came today. Here.
Eat up.
- Thanks.
- Have some soup.
Mom, let him eat
what he wants.
Mrs. Lin, I'll eat whatever you give me.
She's stubborn,
and has a sharp tongue.
Be patient with her.
Get married soon.
No problem.
We broke up ages ago.
I'm not marrying him.
Fighting out of spite
is perfectly normal.
Aren't you fine now?
Look.
He Han is sitting
right here and eating with us.
Please talk some sense into her.
If things don't work out
with her boyfriend,
she can come back to me anytime.
Do I have a boyfriend?
Can you tell me?
Could you please stop making things up?
He Han.
You shouldn't marry Zhanqiao.
She's not worthy of you.
As a father,
I shouldn't say this.
But as your friend,
your confidant,
I have to be honest.
My dad makes a good point.
I don't mind that.
This new boyfriend He Han mentioned...
What does he do?
An up-and-coming young author.
His writing is mediocre.
But he is quite handsome.
He's probably relying on Lin Zhanqiao
to top the charts.
Don't be fooled.
He might just be using you.
He has natural talent.
He was born to write.
With just a few casual updates,
he can instantly
dominate the top of the charts.
Mom, let me tell you,
I've been in this industry a long time.
A naturally gifted writer like him
is one of a kind.
Absolutely unique.
Top of the charts?
Does he write better than He Han?
That's impossible, Mr. Lin.
I haven't been writing lately.
I'm on hiatus.
Good thing you're on hiatus.
Otherwise, getting crushed by a rookie
would be
humiliating.
Being a good writer
doesn't make him a good boyfriend.
Who doesn't love a genius?
Beauty is in the eye of the beholder.
What's his name?
Gu Yan.
Gu Yan?
That's not a good name.
Right?
Mr. Lin, look at this.
Are you done?
Let me see, too.
What does he look like?
Look.
Everyone is getting along.
Like this.
What were you thinking?
My new boyfriend?
Gu Yan is my new author.
We have a strictly
professional relationship.
You think everyone is like you?
What did I do?
You mean...
You've only known
Dai Shan for a few days.
And you're flirting with her
before you even started working!
Dipping your pen
in the company ink, huh?
Jealous?
I'm not jealous!
I just despise your character.
Dai Shan
is a bit older than me.
She is thoughtful.
She can solve
a problem so calmly.
Girls my age would rather
stick together 24/7.
They throw tantrums
over every little thing.
They threaten
to break up with me.
First of all.
I only spent every day with you
because of work.
Second.
Those "little things"
were the straw
that broke the camel's back.
I put up with you over and over again.
Third.
Even though we used to
break up and get back together a lot,
that was because
I had feelings for you.
But this time,
we broke up for good.
Why so defensive?
I was talking about Mimi.
I know.
Our issues weren't entirely your fault.
I had my flaws, too.
Not entirely my fault?
It was 50/50.
Thank you for today.
I appreciate your kindness.
But you keep coming after we broke up.
I hate that.
I always have a reason for finding you.
Even though we broke up,
if I see an issue,
I still have a responsibility
to warn you.
Just like today.
Right? It's no big deal.
Thank you for that.
Never do it again.
Lin Zhanqiao.
Do we have some deep-seated
hatred for each other?
Is there a need to cut each other off?
Unless you admit
you can't let me go.
Seeing me still messes
with your emotions.
I admit it.
I still care about you a lot.
You already have a girlfriend.
I'm looking for a new boyfriend too.
We should stop talking about this.
Do you really believe
I'm dating Dai Shan?
It's all fake.
That was just to deal with Mimi.
So you and Mimi were real?
I never touched her.
Why are you here?
To pick you up.
Heading back to the office?
I'll take a cab.
Don't look
for a new boyfriend online.
Too many scammers.
You're that worried?
You came all the way to pick me up.
What if you two got back together?
I can lose a boyfriend.
But I can't afford to lose
a star author.
You underestimate yourself.
I bought this car
just to show how much I value you.
It doesn't matter if I look bad.
But you need to look good, right?
Thanks, boss.
Lin Zhanqiao got
Zhiyuan's venture capital.
Did you know?
Good for her.
With just one Gu Yan.
What does that tell you?
That Gu Yan is a heavy hitter.
It shows that this money
isn't for Gu Yan.
It's for Lin Zhanqiao.
By producing a Gu Yan,
she proved her own capability.
She doesn't rely on you,
He Han, to make a career.
On the contrary,
you go on hiatus right
after a breakup.
People are saying that
without Lin Zhanqiao,
you can't write a single thing.
So we need to prove ourselves.
On your first day back,
we need a big win.
Okay. Don't worry.
Revise it.
What is this?
Who made these annotations?
The AI evaluation system I'm using.
Writing a novel based on AI evaluation?
Don't underestimate it.
The developers used
massive amounts of fiction
and reader feedback.
It's proven to predict reader tastes...
A Lotus is a Lotus.
It wasn't created
just by studying
masses of car design data.
You don't have to agree with it,
but you shouldn't ignore it.
Hi, Ms. Lin.
Ms. Lin.
You didn't go back?
Where are you staying?
At a friend's place.
It isn't a long-term solution.
No.
Ms. Lin, life has
no long-term solutions.
Only long-term wandering.
He Han's sentimental lines
are nice to read.
Using them to guide your life
is meaningless.
While you're "wandering,"
others are driving luxury cars.
By the way, He Han asked
if you were here yet.
He has something to drop off.
Tell him not to bother.
I don't need anything from him.
What are you waiting for? Go.
Milk tea is on me today.
Once the investment contract is signed,
we'll celebrate with champagne.
Thanks!
Thank you!
Thanks, Ms. Lin.
You're the best.
Thanks.
The financial strain
and resignations
have made recent days
incredibly tough
for all of us.
We barely had the budget
to sign new authors.
But thankfully,
things are about to change.
So please, get ready to kick off
our next phase of work.
Okay.
Gu Yan is our star right now.
But to be safe,
we shouldn't put all our eggs
in one basket.
Who knows if he'll turn
into another He Han?
Lawyer Bei has included strict clauses
in Gu Yan's contract.
Ms. Lin, don't you think
our line of work
is a bit different from others?
Just suppose
he starts slacking off
or writing garbage.
Then what?
Authors on the rise don't
have the luxury to slack off.
And once they're past that stage?
We make sure we always
have new rising stars.
Mantou will handle the coordination.
Fragile will keep an eye
on the big-name authors.
Scouting for new talent
will be Naobaijin's job.
It might be too much for her.
Zhangzhu, you always
wanted to be an editor.
Why not start now?
Learn the ropes from Naobaijin.
That's amazing! So that means
I can finally work as an editor
and manage my own authors?
Thank you for trusting me with this.
You've got this. Work hard!
Good luck! You can do it!
(Still want the lore book?)
Scouting for rookies is a grind.
Anyway, welcome to the game.
Thank you! Thank you!
♪Please don't let me sense it♪
♪I'm only interested in what's in sight♪
♪Please don't call my name♪
♪I'm still finding
my place in the crowd♪
♪Please don't give me an address♪
♪Let my feet take me where they will♪
Come on in.
I'll stay out here.
Just bring it out to me.
What are you so afraid of?
No one's inside, I promise.
No men or women.
I offered to bring it to you,
but you refused.
Now you had to come here for it.
Come in for some tea
and thank me.
It wasn't easy finding this for you.
Thanks.
At the end of the chapter,
I'll have Gu Yan write a note
thanking you
for providing the lore book.
You...
Anything else?
Won't you open it?
When I get back.
I'll walk you back, then.
Won't you read it?
Just one look.
Just a glimpse is fine.
It's done
in no time.
Go on.
I worked so hard
to get this.
What's wrong with it?
Why are you following me?
You'd know if you looked at it.
Still no?
Impressive.
Fine.
I have other things
to take care of.
Thank you.
I know what's inside.
Thank me after you look.
Then, I'll go.
Mr. He...
For real?
It'll only take a minute.
I thought this was gone.
Fine, I've looked.
Leave now.
Wait.
You said we couldn't enter Guazhou.
You insisted on it.
Is this a new map you made?
Who else?
But you said
that entering Guazhou would ruin
the rest of the story.
How did you get the map?
I meant it was a bad idea for Gu Yan.
If I write it,
I can definitely find a way.
It's interesting, right?
I marked the stages for you.
I see that.
So...
Don't you think you should thank me?
I honestly didn't expect you
to help out with Gu Yan's story.
I've got nothing but time.
Sure, I could be
doing plenty of other things,
but I figured
the bond always remains.
Besides, your parents
were always good to me.
And I suppose it's possible
I wasted a bit of your youth.
But, you have to
take some blame too.
Either way,
it was no trouble.
I'm happy to help.
♪If the sky and the sea
turned upside down♪
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Are you moved?
Do you regret being
so mean and cold to me earlier?
What are you really after?
"Drunk Old Friend"
is a story we wrote together.
Even if you're giving it to Gu Yan,
I don't want to see it become a mess.
♪We met in a thirteenth month♪
♪Held each other in a fifth season♪
Anything else?
Let him realize his limits.
Not every hill can be overcome.
And?
♪Rise like tides that never fall♪
♪If we're caught in a pouring rain♪
I gave him such a great story,
a perfect way to break the deadlock,
and even you,
a brilliant editor.
If he can't write it well,
won't you be disappointed?
Just ask me anything.
I'll tell you everything I know.
♪We're on misaligned tracks♪
♪Running in opposite ways♪
♪Searching all along the way♪
(He Han is just like he used to be.)
(One moment
he's dousing me with ice water,)
(the next,
he's making my heart bloom.)
(After the breakup,)
(I'm learning to desensitize.)
♪In another time and space♪
♪We'll stay and walk together
till we grow old♪
(Guazhou)
(Use jade to open the door.)
(Break the seal.)
(Search for Buddhist artifacts.)
What are you doing?
Mr. He Han.
Using the office as a dorm?
Is this place even livable?
It's so unsafe.
What if something falls and hits you?
There is no ventilation.
You're breathing in all this dust.
I...
just...
It's only for a few days.
Once I find a roommate,
I'll move out.
Pack your things and come with me.
What?
You need a place to stay.
Just stay at my place.
It's the least I can do for a fan.
No, no. That's not right.
You stay at a hotel.
You're at a hotel...
How can I go there with you?
No, this is totally inappropriate.
I...
That place isn't right for me.
"That place"?
What are you thinking?
You read too many novels?
Do you think I'm some kind of creep?
Sure, I like pretty girls.
That's because I'm a normal man.
It doesn't mean I'm a pervert.
I'm almost your father's age.
Though I guess
that doesn't mean much these days.
Plenty of creeps
are older than your dad.
- Maybe even your own dad...
- No, no!
Mr. He Han, you're my idol.
How could I ever think you were...
A creep?
Look, that hotel room
is expensive. I can't afford it.
I don't want
to ask my dad for money.
Is that all?
That's not a problem.
I'm a VIP there.
I have plenty of points saved up.
I can use those points.
If it makes you feel better,
pay me what a hostel costs.
How about thirty yuan a day?
Thirty yuan?
Fine, twenty?
No.
Thirty yuan is way too little.
It's fine.
It's not like you're making a fortune.
Enough, it's settled.
Leave that junk behind.
Come on. You just said I was your idol.
Will you listen to your idol?
Stop stalling and let's go.
You'll stay here.
I'm right next door.
Do you usually write in your room,
or at the café downstairs?
Depends on my mood.
I'm on a break anyway.
If you need anything,
just call the front desk.
Thirty yuan a day.
Just wire it to me every Monday.
Get some rest.
Okay.
One more thing.
Don't tell your boss
you're staying here.
Okay.
Thank you, Mr. He Han.
(Transferring funds to
"Great He Han")
Are you Ms. Zhou?
Yes.
Delivery for you.
Thank you.
(As you grow stronger,
the past will seem smaller.)
Hey, just got off work?
I'm so sorry
you have to see the house now.
Take your time.
No worries.
Look, young lady.
You know
the market is rough right now.
Normally, if you weren't in a rush,
I wouldn't suggest selling yet.
It's an emergency.
If you're in a rush,
you're not going to get top money.
I need at least seven million.
With this interior?
I think 6.3 million is fine.
If we wait a bit,
it might be possible.
I can't wait.
How about a month?
A week.
Impossible.
Seven million net.
We split the extra 60/40.
So, 6.3 million?
I could try to push for that.
Well?
Let me think about it.
Sure. Go ahead and eat.
Call me when you've decided.
Take care.
I'll head out then.
(7:42 PM, Zhao Lanxin:
Are you free tonight?)
Why are you here?
You never replied to my text.
I was worried about you after today.
Come on in.
You're an independent,
successful adult now.
You're not
that helpless child
under her thumb anymore.
She doesn't have power over you now.
Whatever you love,
it's okay to love it.
This is your favorite color.
You deserve the most beautiful colors,
the best clothes,
and jewelry.
All of it.
You deserve
to be more beautiful than anyone.
Can you paint nails?
Not really.
But I'm willing to try for you.
(Guazhou)
(Underground Black Market)
(The Flaming Arena)
What do you think?
It looks really useful.
But He Han wrote this.
Can I use it?
Of course.
Not only can you use it,
you should write down any questions
you have about the plot.
I'll take them to him for a Q&A session.
Is he joking?
He said that,
so I take it seriously.
Forget it.
I'm not him.
If I write his story,
it has to be done my way.
Keep an open mind.
Yours or his, it doesn't matter.
Just go with the best idea.
What if he's leading me
in the wrong direction?
What, then?
He won't.
He's too proud for that.
He doesn't play petty games.
What he really wants is
to hand you the blueprint,
and still have
the readers prefer him over you.
You don't buy it.
Fine.
I'll finish eating
and write some questions.
Needed upstairs?
I said I'm not doing the raid.
Everyone, get in position!
Why are you just standing there?
Team 1 healers, hurry up!
Don't just stand there!
Group up and push!
Throw your items right at the start!
Don't just charge in alone.
Is this your first day playing?
Tell me!
Hurry up, Team 1! Team 1!
I'm talking to you, Team 1!
Hurry up, don't just stay there.
Let me take over. Take a break.
Healers, heal! DPS, focus!
What are you all staring at?
Do you want a red-carpet welcome?
I've had it.
Not one player is doing their job.
Know your positions!
Get into your positions!
Stop standing there!
Does no one know their job?
What?
Come outside. Now.
What's your problem?
Get upstairs.
I told you, I'm busy today.
I'm not going.
Oh, so you just decide that
like you rule the world?
There's work at the cafe.
We're dealing with the cafe first.
Let's go.
You...
What has gotten into you?
I said I'm not going!
Since when do you get to boss me around?
Since you lost your conscience!
Alright, sorry.
Please calm down.
I don't care who calls the shot here.
But I promise you,
I only need one hour.
Once I finish up
the work with him, I'll leave.
Ms. Lin.
You'd better stay out of this.
Wang Hai, listen.
You need to think about
what really matters.
Now, get upstairs.
Move.
I'm not going! Just go back!
- Let's go.
- What are you doing?
- Go back!
- Stop it!
Who told you to come down?
Get back up there. Move.
Why are you grabbing me? Grab him!
He's acting so high and mighty.
Take it out on him!
I'm angry
because you're always making trouble!
Get upstairs. Now.
Go!
Let's go!
Fine!
Stop pulling. I can walk.
I'm done with this. I'm done.
I'm sorry for the scene.
It's fine. How about it?
I'll head out.
We're done for today anyway.
And...
read the lore book
and get back to me tomorrow.
Sorry, San Mei.
You two need to
sit down and talk this through.
Whether online novels or gaming,
you need to decide your path.
I'll see you out.
I'm sorry.
It was bound to happen.
Better now than later.
My ride's here.
Head back inside.
I'm so sorry.
I'll have Er Jiu apologize.
Stop playing.
Go to bed.
Forget the practice.
I'm logging on.
Wait.
Let the DPS lead.
Healers, stay back.
Just focus on the heals.
On your left.
(4:35 AM)
(Zhou Mei: Just woke up.)
(You left at 3:00 AM?)
Hello.
And you are?
Where's He Han?
He's up. In the bedroom.
That girl out there...
Wait. It's not like that.
That's Lin Zhanqiao's assistant.
You've taken
Lin Zhanqiao's assistant, too?
Is this revenge against her?
Stop talking nonsense. I said no.
She had nowhere to stay.
I got her a room nearby.
She asked to have breakfast
and some advice.
That's it.
Does Lin Zhanqiao know
that her assistant is here?
If no one here talks,
she won't find out.
Sorry.
Am I interrupting?
No.
Ready to eat?
Yes.
Is your friend joining us?
No, thanks.
Get her some coffee.
Thanks.
Sure.
He Han?
Coming.
Let's eat together.
Shrimp dumplings.
Zhangzhu, get dressed.
See you at the office.
- Ms. Lin, let me explain.
- Save it.
I'll go.
Lin Zhanqiao!
Sorry.
Thanks.
♪Watch my words come alive in bloom♪
♪Unleash six states in a chain of blows♪
♪See a genius born to soar♪
♪Rising high where the wide skies glow♪
♪If you can catch my shadow♪
♪You can cross the world and roam free♪
♪Your next stop in your heart♪
♪Must be me at the top♪
♪Neon lights glaring bright♪
♪Lighting up every hidden place♪
♪I once climbed rooftops all alone♪
♪Searching for the stars above♪
♪Until I saw your eyes aglow♪
♪Shining through the city lights♪
♪Then I knew♪
♪This was me♪
♪The legend I had chased all along♪
♪Never Stop♪
♪From the city streets♪
♪From the sea of stars♪
♪Never Stop♪
You even came after my assistant.
I thought you hated roommates.
We're not living together.
She's next door.
Think about it. A young girl, homeless.
She's pitiful, right?
I was doing my good deed for the day
anonymously.
Noble, right?
You paid for the hotel?
Of course. She's a fan.
Tell her to move out.
I'll find her a place.
Your place?
Isn't it the same?
Very different.
No. She's still
crashing with someone.
I don't want you to influence her.
I don't want her dad
to lecture me again.
Besides, paying for her room?
People will get the wrong idea.
I'll look after my own assistant.
But thanks.
Don't mention it.
It was nothing.
Glad that's cleared up.
You want to be helpful?
Here's a task.
What?
Didn't you want a challenge?
Gu Yan sure isn't shy.
He's asking for favors
like it's nothing.
He's being polite.
I'm not.
Bring him to me.
I'll coach him personally.
Happy now?
Pajamas?
Hurry up and shoot!
You're a grown man.
Don't be sneaky about it.
Take it properly.
Do a group shot.
Okay.
One, two, three.
Here.
- Thanks, Mr. He Han.
- Thank you.
Okay, bye.
- Bye-bye.
- Bye.
So cool.
Mr. He Han.
I cleared things up with your boss.
Don't worry.
Thank you, Mr. He Han.
Phone.
Phone?
Take your 180 yuan back.
For what?
The room.
You paid for seven days,
but you only stayed one.
Here's the rest back.
We're even.
So, you're kicking me out?
Not me.
Your boss wants you at her place.
Personally,
I think I'm the easier roommate.
Dealing with someone that intense
at work and at home
will drive you nuts.
Take care of yourself.
Thank you, Mr. He Han.
Coming!
Mom.
I'll take that.
About yesterday...
Do you think
I went too far?
Did I embarrass you in front of
your friends?
No.
It's my fault.
At your age,
it's easy to lose your way.
As a woman,
you can't rely on looks
to win over men.
That only leads to misery.
Remember that.
The only thing
that outlasts beauty
is your character.
I'll remember.
Don't think
I'm being too harsh.
When you're my age,
you'll understand.
I know.
Just remember,
everything I do
is for your own good.
I get it.
I can tell.
Those two men from the other day?
They both like you.
But all they see
is your face.
In my opinion,
neither of them is right for you.
That's why I'm not looking to date.
Good.
When you pick a partner,
looks,
status,
and money
don't really matter.
Look at their family background instead.
Remember.
You are a product
of your upbringing.
That's a fact.
Here.
Finish this.
I should get going.
I have a calligraphy lesson to attend.
I had my apple today.
Close the door.
It's okay.
The elevator is here.
(I've been thinking.)
(Everyone's most comfortable level of intimacy)
(is probably different.)
♪If the sky♪
♪And the sea♪
♪Turned upside down♪
♪If a swimming fish♪
♪Fell in love with a flying bird♪
♪If back then♪
♪We had never let go♪
♪We wouldn't be lost in the crowd♪
♪We met in a thirteenth month♪
♪Held each other in a fifth season♪
♪And found our way back whole♪
♪So let this surging love♪
♪Rise like tides that never fall♪
♪If we're caught in a pouring rain♪
♪That's alright♪
♪If we're buried♪
♪By passing years all the better♪
♪At least we still can keep♪
♪This one eternal photograph♪
♪We're on misaligned tracks♪
♪Running in opposite ways♪
♪Searching all along the way♪
♪For the fire of our younger hearts♪
♪And the beauty lost in time♪
♪This time don't lose each other again♪
♪Only after loss♪
♪Do we learn what truly matters most♪
♪In another time and space♪
♪We'll stay and walk together♪
♪Till we grow old♪
♪But still the sky will never♪
♪Turn with the sea♪
♪But still a swimming fish won't♪
♪Fall in love with a flying bird♪